## **MARCELO CASTRO**

e-mail: arquero2006@hotmail.com

Re: Welder

Through this I am applying for the position of "Welder".

I am a welder with more than 8 years of experience in the industry, qualified to cut and weld metals and other materials with appropriate equipment to join mechanical structures or parts with great precision, following all safety precautions.

I can contribute dedication, responsible attitude and a great capacity for work; I can also demonstrate a high level of performance, as well as the ability to solve problems and excellence in customer service. I have clear orientation to the results and to the fulfillment of the planned objectives. I am a dynamic person with initiative and I adapt quickly to changes in procedures and new equipment.

For all the above, I am convinced that it could be a valuable contribution with my work for your company. You can obtain additional information about my knowledge and experience in the attached curriculum

Sincerely,

Marcelo Castro

#### MARCELO CASTRO

Toronto, ON M3H/Tel: 416 648 0228 / arguero2006@hotmail.com

#### WELDER

Experience in the construction of structures and metal parts, using designs of planes, instruments and welding machineries in different positions according to specifications and Technical Standards. Extensive knowledge of various welding techniques, including TIG welding, oxy-fuel welding and arc welding.

## **QUALIFICATIONS**

- Read and interpret plans to generate the welded joint or metal cutting.
- Prepare and operate equipment to make welded joints and cut materials
- Operate manual or semiautomatic flame cutting equipment.
- Operate metal forming machines such as brakes, shears and other machines to straighten and bend metals.
- Extensive knowledge of various welding techniques, including TIG welding, oxy-fuel welding
- Work under safety regulations

## **SKILL**

Spanish native / English second language

# **EXPERIENCE**

WELDER Abr 2019 – Dec 2019

### **BDM Railing**

- Elaboration of stairs, windows, doors, closings, fences, plates for the construction.
- Safe handling of tools.
- Handling of automatic and manual cutting equipment.
- Handling of welding equipment Mig Tic and electric
- Planning work orders according to specifications.

WELDER May 2018- Nov 2018

### Atlas Iron Railing

- Elaboration of stairs, handrails, windows, doors, fences, plates for the construction
- Safe handling of tools.
- Handling of equipment for automatic and manual cutting and closing, hydraulic hammer, punching machines, bending machines, etc.
- Planning work orders according to specifications.
- Polishing of parts.

WELDER May 2017- Aug 2018

# Iron Railing

- Elaboration of stairs, handrails, windows, doors, fences
- Safe handling of tools.
- Handling of automatic and manual closing and cutting equipment, hydraulic hammer, mig machines, electrode.
- Planning work orders according to specifications.

WELDER Jan 2016- Feb 2017

## Multifuel Herreria Soldadura

- Assembly of doors, windows and handrails.
- Handling of tools: hydraulic hammer, cutting machine, polisher, might machine and electrode.

# Admistrador Liquidador

Jun 2010- Mar 2016

## Davorclay CIA, Ibarra Ecuador

- Warehouse manager in charge of monthly and annual inventories.
- Management of the Lifo and Fifo System in the merchandise, reporting products by expiration.
- Head of portfolio recovery of credits granted to customers.
- Administrative head at office level.
- Liquidator and closure of the system in the company.

## **EDUCATION**

Systems Technician Oct 2010

Institituto Superior Tecnologico Ibarra

e-mail: <a href="mailto:arquero2006@hotmail.com">arquero2006@hotmail.com</a>

















